Ajay Ko
So friends, welcome to my
YouTube channel once again and yes,
in this video we will talk about the share market
and we have opened the Guru application,
if you have downloaded the Guru application then that's
great, if you haven't then
you
can download it from the link in the description, so let's go,
in this video I am going to tell you about four such shares
which can
see very good profits on the 12th,
you will have to keep an eye on them, from
where the market is opening, so if it
remains down like this then you can buy these shares, so let's
go and see which are
such shares, first of all we will talk about
HDFC Bank, which as you can see is quite
down, so you can keep an eye on it,
this share started from Rs 1512, eat and now it
is at Rs 1502,
okay friends, this is done with this
share and the second share we will talk about is
ICICI Bank Limited, which as you can see,
its share market closed at Rs 639, it became
Rs 638, and now we will move on to the third
share which is State Bank of
India  The
market opened at Rs 425 and
closed at Rs 423. If it
remains down like this, then you can buy this share on the
12th. Now let's move on to the fourth share
which is non-Canara Bank.
Friends, this share is of Rs 151
and when it started at 150, it gained 90 paise and by the time it
closed it became 151. So these were the four shares
which I have told you about in this video, which
you can keep an eye on on the 12th.
It is hundred percent that we will protest. So
if you liked this video, then
like it, subscribe to it and
share the channel.